<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MASON COMPUTERS Homepage on Mason Computers</title>
    <link>https://masoncomputers.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MASON COMPUTERS Homepage on Mason Computers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>MASON COMPUTERS</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://masoncomputers.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me - All Things Tech</title>
      <link>https://masoncomputers.com/posts/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://masoncomputers.com/posts/about-me/</guid>
      <description>MASON COMPUTERS spawned in 2014 when I began my journey into computer programming. Now that I am about to graduate with my B.S. in Computer Science with a focus in Cyber Security, the time has come to give this site a purpose.
Interested in All Things Tech. If something has electricity flowing, there is a good chance that I have experience tinkering with it.
During my extended time at home due to COVID-19, I have found myself picking up forgotten projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Setup Github Pages with Custom Domain Name</title>
      <link>https://masoncomputers.com/posts/github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://masoncomputers.com/posts/github-pages/</guid>
      <description>This article details the steps needed to add a custom domain name to a github pages website.
Github Pages is a static hosting service that is able to host HTML, CSS, and JavaScript from a git repository on GitHub.
You do not need to have a custom domain if you want to use the GitHub Pages service, your personal site https://ejmason101.github.io will still resolve. This write up is intended to be used as a guide to add any domain to point to the your static site on GitHub Pages</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Topics</title>
      <link>https://masoncomputers.com/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://masoncomputers.com/tags/</guid>
      <description>List of Topics#github #github_pages #google_domains #mason_computers #rig #static_website #web_dev  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>